{
    "subject": "resource/St._James_Church_(Monkton,_Maryland)",
    "predicate": "property/architecture",
    "object": "Georgian",
    "human_readable": "St. James Church in Monkton, Maryland has a Georgian architecture.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.972606897354126,
            "question": "What architectural style is St. James Church in Monkton, Maryland built in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9328867197036743,
            "question": "Is St. James Church a Georgian building?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7417186498641968,
            "question": "Describe the architectural style of St. James Church."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6455286145210266,
            "question": "Where is St. James Church located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48460277915000916,
            "question": "What makes Georgian architecture distinctive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4741279184818268,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of Georgian architecture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4421113431453705,
            "question": "Give an example of another building with Georgian architecture."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41043367981910706,
            "question": "How does the architecture of St. James Church reflect its time period?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36264437437057495,
            "question": "When was St. James Church likely built?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3128308653831482,
            "question": "Are there any famous examples of Georgian architecture in the United States?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=St. James Church in Monkton, Maryland has a Georgian architecture.",
            "html": "dbpedia_976_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was St. James Church likely built?",
            "html": "dbpedia_976_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the architecture of St. James Church reflect its time period?",
            "html": "dbpedia_976_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give an example of another building with Georgian architecture.",
            "html": "dbpedia_976_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_976_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_976_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_976_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_976_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_976_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_976_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_976_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_976_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_976_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_976_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that St. James Church in Monkton, Maryland has a Georgian architecture. The document mentions that St. James Church is a \"vernacular interpretation of Georgian ecclesiastical architecture\" and that it features Georgian architectural elements such as iron tie-bars extending across the interior and a hipped-roof design."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"St. James Church in Monkton, Maryland has a Georgian architecture.\" The details from multiple files indicate that St. James' Church is described as having characteristics of Georgian ecclesiastical architecture and was constructed in 1768 in the Georgian style."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}